https://ertelalsop.com/privacy-policy/

— Main Navigation —Filter Equipment – Plate & Frame Filters – – 20 cm x 20 cm Filter Press
– Filter Rentals
Filter Media – Depth Filter Sheets – – Alpha Media: G Series Depth Filter Media
ErtelAlsop > Privacy Policy
The following Privacy Policy describes the information and privacy practices for ErtelAlsop, ErtelAlsop.com (the “ErtelAlsop Web site”) and all other locations, occasions or events where your personal information is collected by, or on behalf of, ErtelAlsop. When you provide us your personal information, you consent to the information practices described in this policy.
Information Collected by ErtelAlsop
As part of your interaction with ErtelAlsop, we may collect personally identifiable information including name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address.  We may also collect demographic information including industry, process/application and product preferences.
We use the personal information you provide for purposes including, but not limited to:
Fulfilling requests for products or information
Providing customer services
Administering promotions or surveys
Offering new products and services
Sending marketing communications
Sharing of Personal Information
ErtelAlsop does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.
We may share your personal information with certain third parties such as our distributors, service providers and other representatives acting on our behalf for limited purposes.
The third parties with whom we conduct business are authorized to use your information only to perform the service for which they are hired. They are required to abide by the terms of our Privacy Policy including taking reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure.
Choices Regarding Your Personal Information
ErtelAlsop communicates with our customers through multiple channels to keep you up-to-date on offers, best practices and new products or services. Once you provide your personal information, we may contact you through direct mail, e-mail or phone. We may continue to communicate with you through these channels unless you request to stop receiving these communications by opting out.
If you no longer wish to receive these communications, let us know by e-mail with your request. Click Here
Once you have opted not to receive marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order confirmations, and/or other organization-related communications.
Security of Your Personal Information
We use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. ErtelAlsop cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and you do so at your own risk.
Cookies
Like many web sites, the ErtelAlsop web site uses “cookie” technology. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site better.
Clickstream Technology
Our Web server automatically collects clickstream information such as the address (or URL) of the Web site that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, which browser you used to view our site and any search terms you may have entered on our site, among other things.
Our Web site may also use other technologies to track which pages our visitors view. This anonymous clickstream data provides our customers with a better, more secure experience and helps ErtelAlsop understand how visitors use our Web site.
Privacy Policy Changes
ErtelAlsop reserves the right to amend this policy at any time. The amended policy shall become effective and soon as it is posted. You agree to review the privacy policy from time to time. Your continued use of the site will represent your acceptance of the modified policy.
© 2020 ErtelAlsop. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy
